Guide to the Doris Duke Memorabilia Collection, 1898-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Postcards, 1900s-1990s and undated
  The postcards in this series vary widely. Postcards include those relating to Duke Farms that were collected by the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation, postcards collected by Doris Duke, and on a lesser scale postcards sent to Doris Duke.
  - Postcards relating to Duke Farms - Bridges, Buildings, Coach Barn, Cascades/Falls, circa 1900s (1 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Postcards relating to Duke Farms - Fountains, Gardens, Gates, circa 1900s (2 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Postcards relating to Duke Farms - Lakes/Creeks, Other, Residence, circa 1900s (3 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Postcards relating to Duke Farms - Roads, Statues, Well House, circa 1900s (4 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Postcards relating to Rough Point, circa 1920s (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mini postcards of various scenes in the Middle East, circa 1930s (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Variety of postcards collected from all over the world, most likely from Doris Dukes travels, 1930s-1940s (1 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Variety of postcards collected from all over the world, most likely from Doris Dukes travels, 1930s-1940s (2 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Variety of postcards collected from all over the world, most likely from Doris Dukes travels, 1930s-1940s (3 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Variety of postcards collected from all over the world, most likely from Doris Dukes travels, 1930s-1940s (4 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Variety of postcards collected from all over the world, most likely from Doris Dukes travels, 1930s-1940s (5 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Variety of postcards with scenes depicting Hawaiian life, activities, and beaches, 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Postcard sent to Doris Duke from Francisco di Pasirosa[?] while she was in Rome. Includes a prayer on the reverse side, "Don't Quit", 1946 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Postcard sent to Doris Duke from an unknown sender. Probably from someone close to her, as she is referred to as "Daisy" on the postcard, 1968 Oct (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Various postcards of the interior displays at Duke Gardens, 1980s-1990s (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Postcards of various locations and works of art, undated (1 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Postcards of various locations and works of art, undated (2 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Postcards of various locations and works of art, undated (3 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Postcards of various locations and works of art, undated (4 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Postcards from the Aquarium du Musee Oceanographique de Monaco, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Postcards of Heronwood in Upperville, Virginia, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Postcard of Heroes Square, Millenary Monument, Russia, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Postcard of Los Angeles State and County Arboretum, Arcadia, California, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Postcard of Lynnewood and the Wonder Fountain at Lynnewood, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Postcards of NRF properties such as Trinity Church and Sunken Gardens, "The Elons", undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Postcards of Prescott Farms, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Postcard of Skylark Helicopters in Miami, Florida, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Postcards of Somerville, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Postcards Souvenir Album, du Veritable Arbre de Robinson, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Postcards and traveller information on various locations including Egypt, India, New Zealand, and Spain, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)